http://naegelireporting.com/privacy-policy/

(800)  528-3335(800)  528-3335schedule nowhomeaboutservicesremote depositionscourt reportingvideographyvideo conferencingtrial supportcopying and scanningtranscriptioninterpreterslocationscontactmediaaffiliates or resourcesawardspressblognaegeli newsonline bill payPRIVACY POLICY | Naegeli Deposition and TrialProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the https://naegeliusa.com/ and NAEGELI Deposition and Trial and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to NAEGELI Deposition and Trial include https://naegeliusa.com. The NAEGELI Deposition and Trial website is a full-service court reporting and litigation support firm site. By using the NAEGELI website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationNAEGELI may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NAEGELI. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NAEGELI website.NAEGELI encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NAEGELI so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. NAEGELI is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NAEGELI website.Use of your Personal InformationNAEGELI collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.NAEGELI may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NAEGELI and its affiliates. NAEGELI may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.NAEGELI does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.NAEGELI may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NAEGELI, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.NAEGELI may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NAEGELI, in order to determine what NAEGELI services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NAEGELI to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.NAEGELI will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NAEGELI or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NAEGELI; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NAEGELI, or the public.Use of CookiesThe NAEGELI website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NAEGELI pages, or register with NAEGELI site or services, a cookie helps NAEGELI to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NAEGELI website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NAEGELI features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NAEGELI services or websites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationNAEGELI secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Children Under ThirteenNAEGELI does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.Opt-Out & UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NAEGELI by contacting us here:
– Email: contact@naegeliusa.com
– Phone: 800.528.3335
Changes to this StatementNAEGELI will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NAEGELI encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NAEGELI is protecting your information.Contact InformationNAEGELI welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NAEGELI has not adhered to this Statement, please contact NAEGELI at:NAEGELI Deposition and TrialCorporate Headquarters111 S.W. Fifth Avenue, Suite 2020Portland, Oregon 97204Email Address:contact@naegeliusa.comTelephone Number:800.528.3335Effective as of January 1, 2016ONLINE BILL PAYresourcesReport an errorLocationscontactCorporate Headquarters111 S.W. Fifth Avenue,Suite 2020Portland, OR 97204 USA(800) 528-3335aboutBlogCareersTerms of ServicePrivacy PolicyfollowFacebookLinkedinTwitter© 2019 NAEGELI Deposition and Trial | All Rights Reserved
